♪ ♪ [ Violins , lyrical ]
♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
♪ ♪ [ Ethereal female voices vocalizing ]
[ Gasps ]
♪ ♪ [ Suspenseful ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Scream echoing ]
[ Man on radio ] It 's 47 degrees right now . It 's 7 : 17 .
- [ Woman moaning ] - Sports news coming up at 25 after the hour ...
And Jack Walters will be having that exclusive interview with Billy Martin ...
And you know that could be fireworks .
Best bet for you folks coming in from Jersey : Do whatever you got to do ...
To use the Holland rather than the Lincoln tunnel .
The backup there at the Lincoln is already a nightmare .
- We 're looking forward to some bright blue skies all day today ... - Oh , yes . Yes . Yes .
With sunshine and highs this afternoon in the upper 50s .
Especially in the city , it could get up near 60 .
Enjoy it while you can . Old man winter 's ...
Gonna be lowering the net any day now .
Lows tonight in the upper 30s with frost ...
In some of the colder regions upstate .
You 're listening to Willie Craig on prn-fm 93 .
And if your clock radio is set to go off at 7 : 18 ...
It should be doing that right about now .
- Start every day with music here on prn . - [ Shower running ]
This is a cut from the new pandemonium album lady Stevie .
[ Clicking , beeping ]
Peter , you 're supposed to be ready in half an hour !
- Ready for what ? - We 're going to the museum today , and -
mom , I can 't go . I need the rest of vacation to finish this .
We made these plans a week ago , remember ?
I know , but I 'm way behind my schedule . I 'm sorry .
Peter , have you been up all night again ?
Morn , the city science championships are next week .
Turn that thing off .
Put that down and look at me .
[ Long beep ]
[ Sighs ] We made a little deal , didn 't we ?
You know I 'm very proud and excited about your project ...
But I don 't want you working all night on it .
I know . I know . I 'm sorry .
Mom , this is the most incredible thing I 've ever built .
I mean , this carries .
It carries ? Carries what ?
Binary numbers . It can hold up to a 20-digit figure .
Wait a second . You said it can carry , and it holds too ?
It does both . That 's the whole point .
There isn 't a circuit like this in any of my books .
I 've invented it .
Well , that 's great .
That 's great , Peter .
What are you gonna call it ?
- I don 't know . - Well , come on .
Everybody knows that when you invent ...
Or discover something , you get to name it .
Like , um , a Napoleon .
A what ?
The French pastry . It was named after Napoleon .
Napoleon invented pastry ? I thought he was a general .
Well , you can 't fight battles all the time .
He baked as a kind of relaxation .
Are you okay , mom ?
Listen , no more all-nighters , okay ?
Okay .
What is this called , anyway ?
It 's a Peter , of course .
That is , if I ever get it finished .
Okay , I 'll let you skip it this time ...
But only if you promise not to work all night .
Okay . I promise .
I promise ! All right ?
Grandma 's gonna be very disappointed ...
But it 's all right .
I 'll explain that you 're working on your Peter .
[ Snorts , chuckles ]
Hmm .
[ Clicking , beeping ]
- [ Horns honking ] - [ Dog barking ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Latch buzzing ]
There 's someone at the front door . Yes .
Between 11 : 00 and 12 : 00 Thursday , right ?
Fine . Bye .
Kate ! Good to see you .
Mary 's on vacation , so I have to be my own receptionist .
- How am I doing ? - I hope you 're not gonna keep me waiting .
I want to get to the museum early .
I have to be at lunch by 12 : 30 with Mike and his mother .
No waiting . Go right in . The doctor will be with you shortly .
So ...
What 's happening ?
[ Spoon rattling in cup ]
My mother 's driving me crazy , as usual .
- Did you talk to her ? - Mm-hmm .
She 's hinting around about surprising me for my birthday .
Ah . She 's going to come up from Florida , is she ?
That 's her surprise .
How do you feel about seeing her ?
Well , I feel ...
I should want to see her .
It 's been six months since we 've been down there ...
But she 'll just ruin my birthday .
And it 's my day , not hers .
Well , now , think .
What are our options ?
I could make up an excuse and tell her not to come .
Mm-hmm .
No , I can 't do that .
And let 's not forget it 's supposed to be a surprise .
Anyway , it 's not her . It 's just ...
I don 't feel up to it , or her , or anything .
How are things going with Mike ?
- Fine . - Good .
No , they 're not fine . What a dumb word that is .
He gave me one of his ...
Wham-bang specials this morning , and I 'm mad at him .
Isn 't that right ? Shouldn 't I be mad ?
Yeah .
Did you tell him ?
- What ? - That you were mad at him .
Of course not .
I moaned with pleasure at his touch .
Isn 't that what every man wants ?
I don 't know . Is it ?
Don 't start that stuff with me .
Don 't you think you 'd feel better if you snapped at Mike instead of me ?
Think about where your anger is going .
I 'm sorry .
Stop apologizing and tell Mike he makes you mad .
Tell him he stinks in bed ?
Does he ?
- Yes . - Then tell him .
Maybe there 's something wrong with me .
There 's nothing wrong with you .
- Do you find me attractive ? - Of course .
Would you want to sleep with me ?
Yes .
Then why don 't you ?
Because I love my wife ...
And sleeping with you isn 't worth jeopardizing my marriage .
Is it worth it to you to jeopardize yours ?
I don 't know .
[ Woman laughing ] I 'm sorry .
Okay . Come on , look at the pictures .
[ Man ] This is so boring .
[ Woman ] Look at the pictures . Come on , Jim , look at the pictures .
That 's what we came for .
Hi .
First time here ?
[ Woman ] Stop it !
[ Laughing ] Cut it out .
[ Child ] Mommy !
- Mommy ! - You stop it !
I told you to stand there and be still for one minute !
♪ ♪ [ Violins , suspenseful ]
♪ ♪ [ Intensifies ]
[ Gasps ]
[ No audible dialogue ]
♪ ♪ [ Violins , urgent ]
♪ ♪ [ Crescendoing ]
♪ ♪ [ Driving ]
♪ ♪ [ Ends ]
[ Kate ] I 'm sorry .
I shouldn 't have been so rude . Thank you for picking up -
♪ ♪ [ Violins , lyrical ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Moaning continues ]
[ Orgasmic moaning ]
- [ Kate screams ] - [ Car horn blaring ]
♪ ♪ [ Ends ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Siren wailing ]
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Computer clicking ]
[ Sportscaster on TV , indistinct ] - Hello ?
Who is this ?
♪ ♪ [ Dramatic ]
- ♪ ♪ [ Ends ] - [ Baby crying ]
[ People talking , faint ]
[ Elevator door opens ]
[ Groans softly ]
[ Elevator slows to stop ]
[ Whispering ] It 's not polite to stare .
♪ ♪ [ Slashing ]
[ Gasps , screams ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Moaning ]
Oh ! No !
No ... no .
[ Screaming ]
So you really think auditron 's going up ?
Well , I got it from a very good source .
[ Kate screaming ]
♪ ♪ [ Slashing ]
- Double , huh ? - You didn 't hear it from me .
You know what ? I 'm gonna give my broker a little call .
Jesus !
Well , what about -
[ Mouthing words ]
[ Screaming ]
No ! Wait !
Please , you don 't understand !
Call the police . Wait !
Please , call the police !
Call the police ! Somebody call the police !
- [ Answering machine beeps ] - Dr. Elliott , this is Lou Freeman .
I 'm still in Chicago .
I won 't be back in time for our appointment on Friday .
I 'll give you a call on Monday , okay ?
[ Beeps ]
Robert , call George . I 'll be home over the weekend .
[ Man breathing heavily ] This is Bobbi .
You won 't see me anymore ...
So I 'm gonna have a little session with your machine .
Oh , doctor , I 'm so unhappy .
I 'm a girl inside this man 's body ...
And you 're not helping me to get out .
So I got a new shrink . Levy 's his name ...
And he 's gonna sign the papers so I can get my operation .
Oh . I borrowed your razor , and -
well , you 'll read all about it .
Some blonde bitch saw me , but I 'll get her .
[ Breathing heavily ]
Remember , if he calls you ...
You better tell Levy I 'm okay .
[ Singsong ] Don 't make me be a bad girl again .
[ Line clicks ]
[ Beeps ]
Dr. Elliott , this is Mrs. Peters .
I just wanted to confirm our appointment for tomorrow .
2 : 00 , right ?
[ Continues , indistinct ]
[ Man on answering machine ] This is detective Marino from the 13th precinct .
One of your patients ...
Kate Miller , was killed tonight .
I wonder if you ' d stop at the precinct and ask for me .
- I got some questions I think you can help me with . - [ Line clicks ]
[ Chatter over police radio ]
[ Phone ringing ]
Are you sure ?
- Mm-hmm . - Okay .
- Positive ID . - Mm-hmm .
Hey , Eddie .
Take this to the lab and get pictures made .
- Yeah . - Keep an eye on her purse .
- We got her booked . - Detective Marino ?
- Yeah ? - I 'm Dr. Elliott .
Oh , doctor .
Would you have a seat outside my office in the corner ?
- I 'll be right with you . - All right .
Give me three copies , and I 'll take care of the paperwork .
[ Woman ] Why don 't you let go of me , will ya ?
Are you Kate Miller 's son ?
I 'm Dr. Elliott , your mother 's doctor .
Why do you have to be here ?
I made Mike bring me .
He 's , uh , identifying the -
my mom wouldn 't be dead if I 'd gone with her .
Oh , you shouldn 't feel responsible for your mother 's death .
If you talk about it , I might be able to help .
- Do you know who killed her ? - No .
- Then you can 't help , can you ? - Not now , maybe .
But later , if you want someone ...
To talk to about all this , ask your father to -
no , he 's not my father . My father was killed in Vietnam .
Take this .
You can call me anytime .
I 'm always there all day long . I 'm usually -
okay , doctor , let 's talk in here .
Call me .
[ Marino ] She was picked up by lockman at the museum .
She spent the afternoon at his place ...
And was chopped up in the elevator on the way out .
That girl out there saw the murderer .
[ Dr. Elliott ] That 's terrible .
- Do you know who it is ? - Some broad .
- A woman ? - Yeah .
Miss Blake didn 't get a great look at her face ' cause she had on big sunglasses .
Is there anything I can do to help ?
Yeah . When you spoke with Mrs. Miller ...
Did she say she was gonna meet anybody ?
- No . - Hmm .
- Did she leave your office with anybody ? - No .
- What was she seeing you for ? - Nothing too serious .
She had problems with her marriage , and I was helping work them out .
- What kind of problems ? - Are you married , detective Marino ?
- Yeah . - Children ?
- Two sons . - When was the last time you had intercourse with your wife ?
What the fuck is it to you ?
That 's exactly how I feel about your questions concerning Mrs. Miller .
Hey , look , doctor ...
We got a brutally murdered woman here ...
Who passed the point of being embarrassed ...
By anything you might tell me .
I guess you 're right .
I 'm sorry . I 'm not used to discussing a patient 's case with outsiders .
I 'm not an outsider , I 'm a cop !
Let 's make it easy for you . Was she lookin ' to get killed ?
- You mean , was she suicidal ? - Yeah .
- No . - So why did she pick up this lockman character , huh ?
- He could 've been a killer . - But he wasn 't .
Yeah , but the next guy might 've been . " If at first you don 't succeed " ?
- You think she wanted to get killed ? - Don 't you ? Hmm ? Look .
We got some hot-pants broad cruisin ' around for some action .
The guy she picked up went down on her in a cab , for chrissake .
I got a blow-by-blow description from the cabbie .
After she finishes with him ...
She comes on to some weirdo in the elevator ?
[ Chuckle ] Hey , there 's all kinds of ways to get killed ...
In this city if you 're lookin ' for it .
Well , yes , she did have a problem about her sexual worth .
And this morning ...
She asked me if I was attracted to her .
Yeah , but you 're not a psycho .
You do know some , though , don 't you , doc ?
Yes , of course . I do some work at bellevue .
Could she have met one of these nuts at your office ?
Some kind of weirdo she could 've turned on that might 've followed her ?
The term we use , detective Marino , is not " weirdo " ...
But " a person suffering from emotional dysfunction ...
And a problem of maladaption . "
And they never come to my office .
Are you sure ?
How about a new patient ?
I mean , how do you know how nuts they are until you see ' em ?
That 's possible , but hardly likely .
Doctor ...
You 're not protecting one of your patients , are you ?
Absolutely not .
Well , doc , you gotta look at it my way .
See , we got no leads except a witness ...
Out there who maybe should take . ..
A look at your patients that were around that morning ...
And that way I can be absolutely sure that my , uh ...
" Weirdo " isn 't your , uh ...
" Person suffering from emotional dysfunctions ...
And problems of maladaption . "
[ Mike ] Peter , come on . Let 's go home .
[ Marino ] Excuse me .
[ No audible dialogue ]
Okay , doctor .
I 'm sorry you 're not more cooperative .
Which means I 'm just gonna have to waste some time ...
In getting a court order to check out your appointment book .
I 'm sorry too , but I feel I must protect the confidentiality of my patients .
Oh , of course .
We 're just two professionals doin ' our job , huh ?
It 's too bad we can 't work together .
- [ Snaps fingers ] - Come on .
Thank you very much for your help . I 'll be in touch .
[ Woman ] Thank you for waiting . This is the answering service .
- Would you care to leave a message ? - Yes , I would .
- This is Dr. Elliott . - How do you spell that ?
E-l-l-i-o-t-t .
What is the message ?
Please say I would very much like to see her ...
And could she call me at my office ?
So , miss Blake ...
Uh , are you still living at 93 Nassau street ?
- That 's right . - Mm . Tell me ...
How did you happen to be in that building that Mrs. Miller was killed in ?
- I was visiting a friend . - Mm . And who was that ?
Well , it 's sort of embarrassing .
I 'd really rather not say .
Why ?
He 's married .
Whoa ! What kind of building is this , huh ?
Everybody 's gettin ' laid after lunch ? [ Chuckling ]
Well , I didn 't say I was " getting laid " ...
To use your expression .
What 's the matter , huh ?
I 'm a little crude for you , huh ?
That 's right .
Look , miss Blake , let 's cut this shit , huh ?
I got all the dope on you right here .
Does this look familiar ? Let me see . March 5th -
" charge : Disorderly conduct .
Solicitation for the purpose of prostitution .
Arresting officer : Durham . Apprehended at the park Avenue hotel . "
- Oh , classy arrest ! - Thank you .
Let 's face it : You 're a whore .
A park Avenue whore , but you 're still a whore .
Now , who were you fuckin ' ?
Fuck you .
No . Fuck you .
You 're no witness , you 're a suspect .
What are you talking about ?
We got a murder weapon with your prints on it .
That 's bullshit . Why would I kill her ?
- You were there with the razor . You tell me . - I told you . A blonde woman -
nobody else saw this blonde woman enter or leave the building .
You didn 't notice if she had wings , did you ?
She was in the elevator . I saw her .
So what were you doing there ?
- I had a job . - Who ?
- You want me to get in trouble ? - You are in trouble .
- Hey , I didn 't kill her . - So who were you fucking ?
Ted . I didn 't get his last name . He 's from out of town .
Oh , that 's great . " Ted from out of town . "
That 's almost as good as " the blonde from the elevator . "
It 's true . He was standing right behind me .
He saw the elevator doors open and that ...
Woman inside , all cut up and bleeding .
I know all about Mrs. Miller . We got her downstairs .
But what about this blonde ? Did he see her too ?
I don 't know .
Look , miss , uh - miss Blake ...
You 're gonna save me a lot of trouble by finding ...
This " Ted from out of town " ...
And getting him in town and downtown and in here ...
To sign his statement as to exactly what he saw and when .
How am I supposed to know where he is ?
If you can 't find him , I sure can 't .
And anyway , you got a lot better motivation than I do : Your ass .
Now get the hell out of here . I 'm giving you 48 hours .
And don 't try to blow town . I 'll be keepin ' tabs on you .
Norma ? Liz .
Where the hell have you been ? I 've been trying to get you all day .
Oh .
Oh , Ted was terrific . That 's why I 'm calling .
I 'd like to see him again . When 's he coming back ?
Two weeks ?
That 's no good . Um -
do you have a number for him ? I 'd like to give him a call .
What do you mean , your escort service doesn 't give out numbers ?
I want to talk to him .
" Trouble " ? No , I 'm not in trouble . I just want to talk to the guy .
Okay . Okay , thanks !
Thanks for nothing .
[ Bell tolling ]
[ Children shouting , laughing ]
[ Clicks ]
[ Bobbi breathing heavily ] You 're just never in .
I 've been out myself , running down that nosy bitch .
[ Breathing heavily ]
I found out where she lives ...
So I 'm just gonna wait right here ...
Until she shows her face .
And then I 'm gonna cut those spying eyes out .
What were you calling me about anyway ?
It wouldn 't be about that murder I read about in the papers ?
Hell of a way to lose a patient . But you shouldn 't try to fuck ' em , doc .
Hi , Max . It 's Liz .
Look , I want to buy 60 shares of auditron .
- What 's it sell for ? - I 'm glad I took care of that cockteaser .
- 15.60 a share ? - You would have done the same yourself .
- That 's 936 - [ Phone ringing ]
Hold it a minute , Max .
I guess that 's why I used your razor .
- Hello ? - But don 't worry about it , doc .
- Hi , Norma . Sorry about yesterday . - Just call the police .
Lost-and-found department .
I know . I was a bad girl .
- Remember , if Levy calls ... - Tonight ?
- Tell him I 'm okay . - I really can 't . Um -
- Norma , hold on a minute . I 'm talking to my mother . - [ Wheezing laughter ]
- Max , when do you need the money ? - That 's funny .
- No , I don 't want to sell anything . - Isn 't it !
- Hold it , Max . - [ Cackling ]
Norma , do you think this guy might go for 500 ?
Great . Hold on just a minute .
I 'm gonna say good-bye to my mother .
Max , I got the money . I 'll have it for you tomorrow .
Okay . Okay !
Hi , Norma . Think you could put together ...
A coffee break and a hot lunch ...
For tomorrow ?
Yeah , I need a thousand dollars for my mother 's operation .
No , it 's nothing serious . I 'm sure she 'll be fine .
- Great . What time tonight ? - [ Phil donahue ] It 's been three to four years since your surgery .
- 8 : 30 . Where ? - I want to show a picture of you ...
- Prior to the - - okay .
- [ Woman ] Where did you find that ? - Anything special ?
[ Donahue ] We stole it from people magazine ...
- Which has an article . - Thank god straight fucks are still in style .
- This is Nancy hunt , the transsexual . - Just in from Cleveland , huh ?
- Isn 't that something ? - I 'll be there .
- You were a war correspondent ? - Among other things .
- And a foreign correspondent in the middle east . - I do have a problem ...
- But it 's nothing serious . - I did a lot of police reporting ...
- And dove on Spanish treasure wrecks . - Thanks , Norma .
- You did a lot of macho things , then . - This is very common among transsexuals .
You find , uh -
when I speak of transsexuals , I tend to speak of male-to-female ...
Because there are a lot more than going the other way .
And an awful lot of them have real macho backgrounds .
I know a police captain , a west pointer ...
A couple of fighter pilots .
You know , most of them tried real hard .
- You were married twice . - Mm-hmm .
- You 're also the father of three children . - Mm-hmm .
Um - so you - you enjoyed a -
I don 't want to say " normal . " I guess that 's a prejudicial way to put it .
But you enjoyed the traditional role of father .
You 've fathered three children , and you have engaged ...
In at least two heterosexual relationships .
Oh , more than that I 've always been a devout heterosexual . [ Laughing ]
[ Knocking ]
- Cleveland ? - Excuse me ?
Room 331 . You 're the guy from Cleveland , right ?
It 's 331 . I 'm from Cleveland .
Well , hi . I 'm Liz from the escort service .
You 're kidding . [ Chuckling ]
- It 's me . - Hi !
Yeah , I 'm glad to meet you .
Well , are you gonna pump me dry here or invite me in ?
Oh , I 'm sorry . Come in . Could I get you anything -
[ horn honking ]
93 Nassau street .
Well , come on ! Let 's go !
♪ ♪ [ Dramatic ]
Look , forget that address I just gave you .
Drop me at Columbus circle .
Could you help me out ?
Someone 's following me .
This is Dr. Elliott again . Did Bobbi pick up my messages yet ?
- [ Woman ] Yes , she has . - She did ?
- Yes , she did . - When ?
I 'm sorry . I wouldn 't know .
Oh . Um ...
Could you give her another message , please ?
Yes . Go ahead .
It is urgent that I see her .
I will be in my office all tonight ...
And after 5 : 00 tomorrow .
♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
What 's the going rate on running lights ?
[ Tires screeching ] [ Horns blaring ]
[ Laughs ] Did I lose her ?
You 're doing swell . Just swell .
[ Horns blaring ] [ Tires screeching ]
But she 's still coming .
[ Horns honking ]
Look , I didn 't deliver , so why don 't you let me take you to dinner instead ?
- All right , you got a date . - Okay .
- I got to go . - Okay . Listen .
- I 'll give you a call . - Yeah , call me .
♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
Excuse me .
- [ Tires screech ] - [ Horn blaring ]
[ Man in car ] Get out of the way !
- Freak , huh ? - [ Drunkenly ] Nearly clipped me , man !
♪ ♪ [ Dramatic ]
♪ ♪ [ Disco on radio ]
[ No audible dialogue ]
What 's she here for ?
You know her ?
Hey , lady , what you lookin ' for ?
A train . They still stop here , don 't they ?
Yeah , they stop here . They stop down there too .
Am I bothering you ?
Naw , you ain 't botherin ' me .
- Good . - But you 're botherin ' me .
- She 's botherin ' you , Sonny ? - Yeah .
- This bitch is botherin ' me . - What are you gonna do about it ?
I 'm gonna break her fuckin ' ass .
Why break it when we can fuck it first , huh ?
- Lady , where you goin ' ? - I don 't want to crowd you guys .
- What are you doin ' down here ? - Give me a break , huh ?
Don 't let her get away !
Come on , man ! Come on !
- Catch her , man ! - [ Exclaiming ]
- Shit ! Get out of the way ! - [ Men exclaiming ]
- Oh ! - Take it easy , lady . This ain 't the rush hour .
Where are you guys when somebody needs you ? I was almost attacked .
- When ? - Right here , now ...
By those punks .
I don 't see nothin ' .
They were right here .
- I thought you said you were attacked . [ No audible dialogue ]
There are , but there 's this blonde that 's been following -
oh , forget it .
[ Man announcing over intercom , indistinct ]
- [ Door opens ] - [ Men chattering ]
♪ ♪ [ Dramatic ]
[ Arguing shouting ]
[ Brakes hissing ]
♪ ♪ [ Slashing ]
- [ No audible dialogue ] - [ Screaming ]
Let 's get the fuck out of here !
[ Screaming ]
The blonde must be one of Elliott 's patients .
I was unloading my camera when I saw her come out of his office , and I followed her to you .
- What was that stuff you sprayed ? - Mace I made at home .
- A simple compound of sodium - - save the Mr. Wizard lecture .
I wouldn 't know sodium from Adam .
It sure worked .
It 's temporary blindness . Only lasts about 10 seconds .
It saved my life .
I know .
I wish it 'd saved mom 's .
You liked your mom a lot , didn 't you ?
Yeah .
I miss her .
Do you want some more coke ?
Yeah . Yeah , thank you .
How do you like my painting ?
It 's , um , very nice .
I bought it a couple years ago for $ 500 .
But you know , it 's really a great investment .
I mean , 10 years from now , it could be worth a million dollars .
More if the artist dies , of course .
[ Chuckles ]
Well , good luck with it .
Thanks .
Doesn 't your father wonder where you are ?
He 's not my father . He 's my stepfather .
I told him I was spending the night at my friend Paul 's .
I 'll take you home tomorrow .
I don 't want to go home . Miss Blake , I 've got
call me Liz , okay ? - Liz , I 've got pictures of that blonde ...
From a camera I hid outside Elliott 's office .
We got to get in , get Elliott 's appointment book , and get her name .
That 's what the police are for . Let 's talk to Marino .
Fine , you talk to Marino . I 'm gonna find out the blonde 's name .
Who do you think you are ? Superman ?
- You 're just a kid , for god 's sake . - I 'm the kid that saved your life .
All right , uh , look .
Let me talk to Marino .
If he cops out , then I 'll help you .
Okay .
But you can 't mention my name . Mike would kill me .
I 'm supposed to be , uh ... [ chuckles ]
Studying for a French exam .
Well , your friend 's covering for you tonight , right ?
Well , I 'm your friend too .
I 'll be the best cover you ever had .
Okay .
You sure you 're gonna be okay here ?
Fine .
Well , here you go .
- Good night . - Good night .
[ Siren winding down ]
Marino , I got to talk to you .
- Mr. Out-of-town turn up ? - No .
- Then send for your overnight bags . - You know I didn 't kill that woman .
You 're still my best bet .
For your information , she tried to kill me last night .
Really ?
Is that supposed to be concern in your voice ?
Hey , I take a professional interest in our citizens knockin ' each other off .
Where did this happen ?
She followed me into the subway . I thought I lost her there ...
But she was waiting - she tried to slash me
any witnesses ? - Yes .
Who ?
- I can 't tell you . - Out of town again ?
No , I just promised I wouldn 't say anything .
This has a familiar ring to it .
Look , Marino , I 'm not interested in your wise-ass remarks .
- Someone 's trying to kill me , and I need help . - I 'll help you . I got a nice cell .
You 'll be very safe . Hey , Eddie . [ Whistles ]
Look , I know the murderer 's one of Elliott 's patients .
- How do you know that ? - She came out of his office .
Did you see her ?
No , not exactly , but I know she came out .
You got to get his appointment book . Her name 's got to be in it .
I hope you make a better hooker than a detective .
- I thought about Elliott 's appointment book a long time ago . - So ?
So you can 't just walk into some shrink 's joint and start goin ' through his books .
You need a search warrant . And judges take a long time ...
Before they let you start snoopin ' around some shrink 's office .
' Course , uh ...
That wouldn 't prevent a paranoid murder suspect ...
From breakin ' in .
You know , uh , searchin ' for some evidence to defend her case .
I get it . You want me to break in for you .
Hey , I don 't want you to do anything illegal .
You can quote me on that . But I 'm bookin ' you tomorrow .
You got it ? Tomorrow .
[ Siren wailing ]
- I 'm Dr. Levy . - How do you do ?
I 'm Dr. Elliott .
What can I do for you , Dr. Elliott ?
- You 're seeing a patient of mine . - That 's right .
- I believe she 's dangerous . - Really ? In what way ?
She 's causing me trouble because I wouldn 't approve her sex-change operation .
What kind of trouble has she caused you ?
She 's threatened me several times over the phone .
She also stole my razor .
Why would she do that ?
Did you read about the woman slashed to death in an elevator ?
- It was on the front page . I could hardly - - Kate Miller , the victim , was my patient !
You don 't think Bobbi had anything to do with that ?
My razor 's gone . Kate Miller was killed with a razor .
- Nobody else could have taken it ? - Doctor , I am not paranoid .
Bobbi has threatened me , she said she was going to hurt me ...
My patient was slashed to death , and my razor 's gone .
You don 't have to be a detective to figure it out , do you ?
Come with me and , uh , we 'll talk to the police .
I 've already been to the police .
I didn 't tell them about Bobbi . I wanted to talk to her first .
I wanted to be absolutely sure it was her .
But she wouldn 't return my calls .
I was hoping you 'd be able to help .
Um , yes , I 'll help .
I 'll talk to her .
If I agree with your diagnosis , we 'll go to the police .
Thank you . Please let me know what happens .
Do you know why Bobbi came to me in the first place ?
No .
Why don 't we go to my office and try to get in touch with her ?
I 'm late for an appointment now .
Why don 't you call me at my office when you 've reached her ?
All right . You 're sure you 'll be at your office ?
Yes , I 'm sure .
I 'll call you there .
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Peter Miller . I left some super 8 film .
There 's four dollars there .
[ Peter ] I timed Elliott 's patients coming out of his office .
The fastest was eight seconds ...
So I set my camera to go off every four seconds so I 'd get a shot of everybody .
That 's her .
[ Liz ] She must be his last appointment .
- We got to get a look in that book . [ Thunder rumbling ]
I know . Marino wants it too . Only , I can get it for him faster .
No legal red tape , just my ass .
Look , I 'll get it . Nobody cares about my ass , right ?
I 'm just a grief-struck kid .
Yeah , but what a kid .
Okay , I got an idea .
- It was very nice of you to see - [ Thunder crashing ]
It was nice of you to see me so soon .
I try to keep my nights open for returning phone calls ...
Or in case a patient needs some extra help .
I was worried about you .
You 've had a terrible experience .
I know .
I didn 't realize it ...
But I 've been having these terrible nightmares .
Oh . What were they about ?
Well -
I have to get a cigarette .
I 'm in this house that I 've never been to before , visiting a friend .
He 's not there .
I 'm watching TV ...
And the doorbell rings .
- It 's a man . ♪ ♪ [ Ethereal female voices vocalizing ]
He 's big , dark .
He says his car broke down and he needs to use the phone .
I believe it and let him in ...
Although I know something 's wrong .
He closes the door ...
Locks it , and takes out a razor .
He says he 's not gonna hurt me .
♪ ♪ [ Ethereal voices continue ]
Then he tells me ...
What he 's gonna do to me ...
[ Thunder crashing ]
And how much I 'm gonna like it .
All the time he 's talking ...
I can see the bulge in his pants .
He orders me to strip .
I do it ...
Keeping one eye on the razor .
He drops his pants .
He forces me down ...
On my stomach .
He spreads my legs ...
Kneels down behind me ...
- And rests the cold blade - - [ Thunder crashing ]
Forcing it -
[ exhales sharply ]
I 'm sorry .
What 's the matter ?
It 's just so dirty .
Why do you say that ?
Look , I know what dirty is , and this is dirty .
Well , why don 't you just talk about it ?
I 'm sure it 's not as bad as you think .
It 's very bad .
And you 're talking to an expert on " bad . "
Oh , really ?
What makes you such an expert ?
- Cause I 'm a hooker . - Ah .
And I 've done most of the bad things ...
You just read about .
Do you like doing these things ?
- Sometimes . - What do you like about it ?
I like to turn men on .
I must do a pretty good job , because they pay me a lot .
Do you ever have sex that 's not paid for ?
Is that a proposal ?
No .
It 's what we psychiatrists call " a question . "
Yes .
- " Yes " what ? - Yes , I do , from men that turn me on .
What sort of men turn you on ?
The mature , doctorly type .
Like you .
Are you sexually attracted to me ?
Yes . Are you ?
- Attracted to you ? - Uh-huh .
Yes .
[ Thunder crashing ]
But this isn 't a social visit , is it ?
You 've come here for help , and my job is to offer emotional assistance .
How about some sexual assistance ?
Do you want to fuck me ?
- Oh , yes . - Well , why don 't you ?
- Because I 'm a doctor , and - - fucked a lot of doctors .
- And I 'm married . - Fucked a lot of them too .
Don 't you think we 're getting off the point ?
- Do you mind if I take off my coat ? - No .
♪ ♪ [ Ethereal female voices vocalizing ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
And the rest too ?
Now , why would you want to do a thing like that ?
Well , because of the size of that cock in your pants .
I don 't think you 're so married .
Well ?
What do you think ?
I think you 're a very attractive woman .
Would you like to touch me ?
Uh , yes and no . Yes , because I 'm
why don 't you ? - I told you why .
Oh , that 's right . You 're a married doctor .
I remember now . I think you 're full of shit .
You do ?
Just because I happen to have personal and professional ethics ?
Look , doc , I think you 're kind of shy .
So , uh ...
I 'm gonna go powder my nose ...
And when I come back ...
I hope to find your clothes right next to mine .
And if not , we can just get back to the mind-fuck .
♪ ♪ [ Ethereal voices continue ]
♪ ♪ [ Suspenseful ]
♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
[ Cries out ]
[ Muffled shout ]
Dr. Elliott ?
- You really are shy , aren 't you ? - [ Pounding on window ]
[ Peter ] Liz ! Liz !
- Behind you ! - [ Pounding continues ]
Liz ! Liz !
She 's right behind you , Liz !
♪ ♪ [ Slashing ]
[ Shot fires ]
♪ ♪ [ Dramatic ]
[ Sobbing ]
♪ ♪ [ Ends ]
- So you had me followed . - That 's right .
You 've met Betty luce , one of our best young police ... [ clears throat ] Persons .
So when I told you I was attacked , you thought I was nuts .
Detective luce told me she lost you at Columbus circle .
I didn 't figure there was another blonde following you . Who would ?
And you wrote me off as a girl with an overactive imagination .
- Somethin ' like that . - And she followed me to Elliott 's .
That 's right .
Thank god . What 's wrong with that guy anyway ?
- [ Dr. Levy ] He was a transsexual . - What ?
A transsexual .
About to make the final step , but his male side couldn 't let him do it .
[ Marino ] " Male side " ?
There was Dr. Elliott , and there was Bobbi .
Bobbi came to me to get psychiatric approval ...
For a sex-reassignment operation .
I thought he was unstable , and Elliott confirmed my diagnosis .
Opposite sexes inhabiting the same body .
The sex-change operation was to resolve the conflict .
But as much as Bobbi tried to get it ...
Elliott blocked it .
- So Bobbi got even . - [ Marino ] By killing Mrs. Miller .
Yes . She aroused Elliott ...
Just as you did , miss Blake .
You mean when Elliott got turned on , Bobbi took over ?
Yes . It was like Bobbi 's red alert .
Elliott 's penis became erect ...
And Bobbi took control , trying to kill ...
Anyone that made Elliott masculinely sexual .
When Elliott came to my office , it was the first time ...
I saw Bobbi 's masculine self .
When he told me that he thought ...
Bobbi had killed Mrs. Miller , he was confessing himself .
I immediately called detective Marino .
So why the hell didn 't you stop me from going to Elliott 's ?
Why ? Because I was at a football game with my kids .
By the time I spoke with Dr. Levy , you were already there .
So you never really thought I killed Mrs. Miller .
No , but I had to get into Elliott 's office ...
To find out which weirdo did ...
So I pressed you into service .
- Are you kidding ? - [ Chuckles ]
I had miss luce there tailin ' you ...
To make sure you didn 't get into too much trouble .
Thanks .
Well , it 's always wonderful ...
To be of some assistance to the police .
Are you kiddin ' ?
So , uh , what 's gonna happen to Elliott ?
Well ?
There 's men and women who think they 're born in the wrong body .
They 're called transsexuals ...
And all they want to do is have their sex changed .
How do you do that ?
If you 're a man that wants to become a woman , you take female hormones .
What do they do ?
Well , your skin softens ...
You grow breasts , and you don 't get hard anymore .
Great .
Sure you want to know about this ?
Yeah , yeah . It 's giving me some , uh ...
Wonderful new ideas for a science project .
Instead of building a computer , I could build a woman ...
- Out of me . - Great idea .
In that case , I 'll give you all the details .
The next step is surgery .
Let me see if I can remember the exact word Levy told me .
Oh , yeah : A penectomy .
- Mm . What 's that ? - Oh , you know -
they take your penis and slice it down the middle .
Yeah , that 's , uh , what I thought it was .
Then , um , castration ...
Plastic reconstruction , and the formation of an artificial vagina .
A vaginoplasty , to those in the know .
[ Wry chuckle ] And I thought Elliott just put on a dress .
He did , and a wig too .
But that 's no good in bed , when you got to take everything off .
What 's gonna happen to him now ?
First he has to recover from the gun wound .
And if he 's ever sane enough to get out of bellevue , they 'll try him .
And guess who 's the star witness .
- You . - Right .
Something I 'm really looking forward to .
Well , I think I 'm gonna stick with my computer .
That sounds like a very good idea .
Look , Liz , um , I got to get home and get to work .
Gee , I 'm gonna miss having you on my tail .
It made me feel kind of safe .
Look , you want to come home with me ?
- I 'd love the company . - Wouldn 't Mike mind ?
Well , Mike 's out of town on a business trip .
We got plenty of room .
Great . I could sure use the vacation .
Good . Good . I 'll get the check .
♪ ♪ [ Suspenseful ]
[ Moaning ]
- [ Choking gasps ] - ♪ ♪ [ Dramatic ]
[ Bones snap ]
[ No audible dialogue ]
[ Whooping , cheering ]
♪ ♪ [ Crescendoing ]
♪ ♪ [ Climaxing ]
♪ ♪ [ Ends ]
[ Man breathing heavily ]
[ Computer clicking , beeping ]
[ Shower running ]
[ Creaking , rattling ]
[ Lock clicks ]
[ Hinges creaking ]
[ Soles squeaking ]
♪ ♪ [ Dramatic ]
♪ ♪ [ Crescendoing ]
♪ ♪ [ Climaxes ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screams ] No ! No ! No ! No !
[ Sobbing ]
♪ ♪ [ Ends ]
♪ ♪ [ Violins , lyrical ]